Armando Lara

COMPUTER SYSTEM ENGINEER

Profile

With a robust background in web and mobile development and **more than 4 years of experience**, I've had worked on diverse projects, where I've consistently demonstrated my ability to innovate and push boundaries. My skill set extends beyond coding and development to encompass creative design, making me a versatile asset in any technology-driven role.

Work Experience

Front End Angular Developer - Haizen Abogados, Arandas, Jal., México

SEPTEMBER 2019 — PRESENT

Design and development of the business control system.

Graphic designer - Extinguidores de los Altos, Arandas, Jal., México

FEBRUARY 2018 — JANUARY 2019

Worked as a designer and printer of customized signals, signboards, printed tarps and decals.

Education

Tecnológico Mario Molina Pasquel y Henríquez Campus Arandas, Arandas, Jalisco

AUGUST 2016 — JUNE 2021

Computer System Engineering - Databases.

Achievements

Internal contest of programming

Computer System Engineer / Tecnológico Mario Molina Pasquel y Henríquez Campus Arandas, Arandas, Jalisco

SEPTEMBER 2016 — SEPTEMBER 2019

Three times winner of the internal contest of programming.

Internal competition of science and technology week

Computer System Engineer / Tecnológico Mario Molina Pasquel y Henríquez Campus Arandas, Arandas, Jalisco

JULY 2016 — JULY 2018

Two times winner of the internal competition of science and technology week.

Contact Info

Email

armandolarae97@gmail.com

Tel:

348 103 6143

Links

<u>Portfolio</u>

LinkedIn

<u>Github</u>

Skills

React **3** years

NextJS **6** months

Angular 4+ years

Flutter **1+** year

JavaScript **3+** years

TypeScript **4+** years

NodeJS **4+** years

NestJS **6** months

MongoDB **4+** years

MySQL **2+** years

Languages

Native Spanish

Advanced English